A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Public Broadcasting, Office Files of Stuart F. Sucherman FA689
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Public Broadcasting, Office Files of Stuart F. Sucherman
1964-1969
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA689
1.2 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material is open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- Subject Files, 1964-1969; I
  Scope and Contents
  Primarily Public Broadcast Laboratory
  - AFTRA, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - American Federation of Musicians, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Directors Guild of America, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Estimated Cost of Operation (Public Broadcast Laboratory), 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Executive Committee (Public Broadcast Laboratory), 1968 (Box 1)
  - Ford Foundation, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
  - NET Administrative, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
  - NET Legal, 1967 (Box 1)
  - NET-PBL, 1967 (Box 1)
  - PBL/NET, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Program Advisory Committee (Public Broadcast Laboratory), 1968 (Box 1)
  - Programming Assignments, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Programming -- General, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Programming Meeting, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
  - Reorganization (Public Broadcast Laboratory), 1968 (Box 1)
  - Right of Privacy, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Speeches and Announcements, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Oct 1967 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Nov 1967 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Dec 1967 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Jan 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Feb 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Mar 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, May 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Aug 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Sep 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Oct 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Nov 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Dec 1968 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Jan 1969 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Feb 1969 (Box 1)
  - Status Reports, Mar 1969 (Box 1)